<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Ian Easter</title><link>https://ianeaster.dev/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Ian Easter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 15:07:20 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ianeaster.dev/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hugo and Netlify</title><link>https://ianeaster.dev/posts/2021/01/12/hugo-and-netlify/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 15:07:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ianeaster.dev/posts/2021/01/12/hugo-and-netlify/</guid><description>Over the last couple of years I have played around with Jekyll, Gatsby, Hugo, among a few others. Hugo, in my experience, required the least amount of work out of me to accomplish my goal. Personally, anything that values the end user&amp;rsquo;s time invest has high marks in my book. I think any software, service, or product&amp;rsquo;s end goal should be to make whatever task easy. For me, Hugo seemed to cover that.</description></item><item><title>:confetti_ball:Happy New Year:confetti_ball:</title><link>https://ianeaster.dev/posts/2021/01/01/happy-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 22:45:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ianeaster.dev/posts/2021/01/01/happy-new-year/</guid><description>A very welcomed Happy New Year to you all and welcome to my personal site.
I&amp;rsquo;ll consider this place as a showcase, note collection, and possibly a source of information.
My primary focus is around Linux, Python, containers and several automation tools. However, I dip into many areas and categories so stick around to see if anything catches your fancy.</description></item><item><title>Welcome</title><link>https://ianeaster.dev/posts/2021/01/01/welcome/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 22:45:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ianeaster.dev/posts/2021/01/01/welcome/</guid><description>As with most new sites and blogs, this is an initial post to christen a new site.
Making sure things work, everything is put together, that sort of thing.
I can be a wordy fellow at times so I&amp;rsquo;ll keep it short and sweet. I will be using this site as a bit of a thought dump, portfolio, show off of sorts. A place to drop down ideas or process how I&amp;rsquo;m working through projects or self learning.</description></item></channel></rss>